direct-offers.com 2016-02-10

# Privacy | Direct Offers

Privacy Policy

We are dedicated to safeguarding and preserving your privacy when visiting our site web site. This Privacy Policy, provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you.

We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.

Information Collected

We do not collect any personal user data or attempt to identify any users. However, when you visit this site, the server records certain statisical information. This includes: the server address, top level domain name, date and time of visit, ,the web pages accessed and the web browser used.. This data is collected for site administration purposes, to help maintain security and for improving the website.

If you join our newsletter, we will collect and store your email address for the duration that you are subscribed.

Use of Cookies

On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our website to our advertisers. Such information will not identify you personally it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

Similarly to the above, we may gather information about your general internet use by using a cookie file. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you.

All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular parts of our website.

Use of Your Information

The information that we collect and store relating to you is primarily used to enable us to provide our services to you. In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:

To improve our website and content

The delivery of our newsletter (if you are subscribed)

Please be advised that we do not reveal any user information to any third parties, but we may, on occasion, provide them with aggregate traffic statistics for our website.

Storing Your Personal Data

We do not store any personal user data. The only data that may be stored is your email address, if you subscribe to our newsletter. We will only keep your email address while you are subscribed. If you unsubscribe, your email address will no longer be stored. We never disclose any email addresses to any third parties.

Email Addresses

If you opt-in to our newsletter, we will store your email address. This is solely for the purpose of sending out our newsletter. We do not sell or disclose email addresses to any third party. Your email address is only kept while you are a subscriber. If you opt-out of our newsletter, your email address is deleted.

Opt-Out

If you are subscribed to our newsletter, you can opt out at anytime. Opt-out links are provided in each newsletter. If you opt-out, we delete your email address and you will not receive any further correspondence from us.

Disclosing Your Information

We never disclose any user information to any third party.

Third Party Links

Our site has links to external sites, which also have their own privacy policies. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them. We recommend you review the privacy policy of any third party site.
